https://judithandjim.com/privacy-statement/

Privacy Statement
Judith & Jim are the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance your experience on our site. You may, however, still navigate our site if your settings reject cookies.
Links Provided To Other Sites
Judith & Jim may provide links to a number of other web sites that we believe might offer you useful information and services. However, those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as Judith & Jim. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the actions of any third parties, including without limitation, any web site owners whose sites may be reached through this Site, nor can we control the activities of those web sites. We urge you to contact the relevant parties controlling these sites or accessing their on-line policies for the relevant information about their data collection practices before submitting any personal information or other sensitive data. If you do not click on the third party banners, there is no way for them to collect information about you.
Your Consent To This Privacy Policy
Use of the Site signifies your consent, as well as the consent of the company for whom you use the Site and whose information you submit (if any), to this on-line Privacy Policy, including the collection and use of information by Judith & Jim, as described in this statement, and also signifies agreement to the terms of use for the Site. Continued access and use of the Site without acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy relieves Judith & Jim from responsibility to the user.
Notification of Changes
Any changes to any of our policies will be posted on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
